next.co.in 2012-12-04

# Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy Is Our Commitment to You**

We value the relationship we have with our customers and are committed to responsible information-handling practices. We take great care in safeguarding your personal information and in complying with all applicable privacy laws and our own internal standards and best practices.

Next.co.in follows the following privacy principles both online and offline in the collection, use, and sharing of customer information:

**NOTICE**

When we ask for your personal information, we will tell you why we need it and what we will do with it.

**CHOICE**

When we contact you for marketing purposes, we will let you know how to remove your name from future marketing efforts.

**SECURITY**

We will use reasonable security measures to protect the personal information we receive from you.

**SHARING**

When we share your information with other companies to help us in providing services to you, we will require them to comply with all applicable legal requirements regarding the privacy of your information.

Next.co.in is a part of Next Retail India Ltd. If you provide information to any of the businesses owned or operated by the group companies, this information may be shared among current or future Next Retail’s entities and subsidiaries.

Each member of Next Retail and/or each Web site established by a member of the Next Retail India Ltd. companies/Group Companies may have its own Privacy Policy which it may modify as needed consistent with these principles.
